<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">Aero DAP TEST</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open" translatable="false">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close" translatable="false">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title" translatable="false">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle" translatable="false">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc" translatable="false">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings" translatable="false">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_venta">Let\'s travel together!</string>
    <string name="botonComprar">Buy Tickets</string>
    <string name="botonCheckin">Check In</string>
    <string name="monedaPago">" Select Payment Currency"</string>
    <string name="clpTexto">" CLP - Chilean Pesos   (This option is only valid for Cards issued in Chile.)"</string>
    <string name="usdTexto">USD - Dollars</string>
    <string name="destinos">Our Destinations</string>
    <string name="oficinas">Commercial Offices</string>
    <string name="bienvenido">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="cancelar">Cancel</string>
    <string name="title_activity_checkin" translatable="false">Checkin</string>
    <string name="tituloCheckin">We are going to fly!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_oficinas" translatable="false">Oficinas</string>
    <string name="cabezeraOficina">If you need personalized attention, you have any questions or problems, you can visit us at our commercial offices.</string>
    <string name="direccionBBA">Arturo Prat Nº 286, office 9, 2nd floor.</string>
    <string name="direccionPUQ">Ignacio Carrera Pinto 1015.</string>
    <string name="horarioBBA1">Monday to Friday from 09:00 to 13:00 and 14:30 to 18:30 rrs.</string>
    <string name="horarioBBA2">Saturdays from 09:00 to 13:00 hrs.</string>
    <string name="horarioPUQ1">Monday to Friday from 8:30 to 18:15 hrs.</string>
    <string name="horarioPUQ2">Saturdays from 9:00 to 13:00 and 15:00 to 18:00 hrs.</string>
    <string name="telefonoBBA">+56672212898</string>
    <string name="telefonoPUQ">+56612229936</string>
    <string name="telefonoTextoBBA">+56 67 2 212898</string>
    <string name="telefonoTextoPUQ">+56 61 2 229936</string>
    <string name="textoMapa">See map</string>
    <string name="tituloOficina">Come visit us!</string>
    <string name="oficinasSubtitulo">Our Offices</string>
    <string name="horario">Office hours:</string>
    <string name="direccion">Address:</string>
    <string name="telefono">Phone:</string>
    <string name="llamar">To Call</string>
    <string name="direccionWPR">Manuel Señoret S/N.</string>
    <string name="direccionWPU">Plaza del Ancla S/N.</string>
    <string name="horarioWPR1">Monday to Friday from 9:00 to 12:30 and 14:30 to 18:30 hrs.</string>
    <string name="horarioWPR2">Saturdays from 09:00 to 13:00 hrs.</string>
    <string name="horarioWPU1">Monday to Friday from 09:30 to 13:00 and 14:30 to 18:30 hrs.</string>
    <string name="horarioWPU2">Saturdays from 09:00 to 13:00 hrs.</string>
    <string name="telefonoWPR">+56612580089</string>
    <string name="telefonoTextoWPR">+56 61 2 580089</string>
    <string name="telefonoWPU">+56612621114</string>
    <string name="telefonoTextoWPU">+56 61 2 621114</string>
    <string name="title_activity_destinos" translatable="false">destinos</string>
    <string name="tituloDestinos">Discover Patagonia!</string>
    <string name="destinosSubtitulo">Our Destinations</string>
    <string name="destinosPUQ">Punta Arenas is the capital of the Magallanes region and the Chilean Antarctic. Founded on December 18, 1848, it is located on the coast of the peninsula of Brunswick, on the continental shore of the Strait of Magellan, and is the southernmost point of the continental mass of America. It is known as the \"Capital of Southern Patagonia\" and be the global gateway to the Antarctic continent.</string>
    <string name="destinosPUQ1">All our regular destinations have as their starting point the city of Punta Arenas.</string>
    <string name="destinosWPU">Puerto Williams is located on the northern shore of Navarino Island, and on the southern shore of the Beagle Channel. It is the capital of both the Communes of Cape Horn and Antarctica and the Province of Chilean Antarctic, and is characterized by being the southernmost administrative settlement on Earth.</string>
    <string name="destinosWPU1">From Monday to Saturday</string>
    <string name="destinosWPU2">Punta Arenas - Puerto Williams: 10:00 hrs.</string>
    <string name="destinosWPU3">Puerto Williams - Punta Arenas: 11:30 hrs.</string>
    <string name="destinosWPR">Porvenir is the capital of the province of Tierra del Fuego, and is the most inhabited city in the Chilean portion of the Isla Grande of Tierra del Fuego. Located next to the Porvenir Bay, it faces the city of Punta Arenas, from which it is separated by the Strait of Magellan. It was founded in the year 1894.</string>
    <string name="destinosWPR1">Monday to Friday</string>
    <string name="destinosWPR2">Punta Arenas - Porvenir : 08:15 / 12:30 / 16:30</string>
    <string name="destinosWPR3">Porvenir - Punta Arenas : 08:35 / 12:50 / 16:50</string>
    <string name="destinosWPR4">Saturday</string>
    <string name="destinosWPR5">Punta Arenas - Porvenir: 08:15 / 12:30</string>
    <string name="destinosWPR6">Porvenir - Punta Arenas: 08:35 / 12:50</string>
    <string name="destinosBBA">Balmaceda is a town near Coyhaique, in the Region of Aysén, being the only one in the area that has an international airport. For its part Coyhaique is the capital and the main urban center of the Region of Aysén. The city was founded on October 12, 1929.</string>
    <string name="destinosBBA1">Tuesday</string>
    <string name="destinosBBA2">Punta Arenas - Balmaceda: 13:30</string>
    <string name="destinosBBA3">Balmaceda - Punta Arenas: 15:30</string>
    <string name="destinosUSH">Ushuaia is a city in Argentina and the capital of the province of Tierra del Fuego, Antarctica and the South Atlantic Islands. It was founded on October 12, 1884. The city is located on the shores of the Isla Grande of Tierra del Fuego that overlook Ushuaia Bay in the Beagle Channel, and is surrounded by the Martial mountain range. Ushuaia is generally considered the southernmost city in the world.</string>
    <string name="destinosUSH1">From November 2, 2018 to March 10, 2019.</string>
    <string name="destinosUSH2">Friday and Sunday</string>
    <string name="destinosUSH3">Punta Arenas - Ushuaia: 14:00</string>
    <string name="destinosUSH4">Ushuaia - Punta Arenas: 15:30</string>
    <string name="destinosDPB">Located in the extreme south of Chile, 450 kilometers south of Punta Arenas and belonging to the commune of Timaukel in Tierra del Fuego. It is an emerging locality and in search of developing a new colony.</string>
    <string name="destinosDPB1">From October 5, 2018 to April 28, 2019.</string>
    <string name="destinosDPB2">Friday and Sunday</string>
    <string name="destinosDPB3">Punta Arenas - Pampa Guanaco: 18:00 hrs</string>
    <string name="destinosDPB4">Pampa Guanaco - Punta Arenas: 19:00 hrs</string>
    <string name="destinosDPB5">* Sale of tickets only in commercial offices.*</string>
    <string name="cabeceraDestinos">More than three decades flying in the southern skies ...</string>
    <string name="cabeceraDestinos1">Regular Flights Patagonia</string>
    <string name="contacto">Contact</string>
    <string name="preguntas">Frequent Questions</string>
    <string name="main">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="nombre">Aerovias DAP</string>
    <string name="title_activity_contacto">Let\'s communicate!</string>
    <string name="cabeceraContacto">"If you have any questions regarding our programs, fleet, services, or flight and itinerary information, do not hesitate to write us. We will approach your inquiry as soon as possible. "</string>
    <string name="contactoSubTitulo">Contact Form</string>
    <string name="contactoCharter">Charter flights</string>
    <string name="contactoAntartica">Antarctic and Patagonia</string>
    <string name="contactoEmpresa">Contact our company</string>
    <string name="contactoReclamo">Complaints, suggestions or congratulations</string>
    <string name="contactoTraslado">Medical rescue</string>
    <string name="contactoRegular">Regular flights</string>
    <string-array name="opciones">
        <item>Charter flights</item>
        <item>Antarctic and Patagonia</item>
        <item>Contact our company</item>
        <item>Complaints, suggestions or congratulations</item>
        <item>Medical rescue</item>
        <item>Regular flights</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="contactoSelecciona">Select an option:</string>
    <string name="contactoNombre">Name</string>
    <string name="contatoMail">E-mail</string>
    <string name="contactoComentario">Message</string>
    <string name="contactoEnviar">Send</string>
    <string name="contactoOk1">We have received your message correctly!</string>
    <string name="contactoOk2">We will answer you shortly.</string>
    <string name="validaNombre">Please enter your name.</string>
    <string name="validaMail">Please enter your email correctly.</string>
    <string name="validaMensaje">Please enter your message.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_preguntas">Looking for answers?</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tarifas">Our Fares</string>
    <string name="tarifasCambiosAntes">Changes before the date of the flight</string>
    <string name="tarifasDevolucion">Refund</string>
    <string name="tarifasCambiosDespues">Changes after the date of the flight</string>
    <string name="tarifasEquipajeMano">Hand Baggage</string>
    <string name="tarifasEquipajeFacturado">Checked Baggage</string>
    <string name="tarifasCambiosAntesSR">Allows changes up to 72 hrs before without charge, after that time NOT allowed</string>
    <string name="tarifasDevolucionSR">Not allowed</string>
    <string name="tarifasCambiosDespuesSR">Not allowed</string>
    <string name="tarifasEquipajeManoSR">5kg</string>
    <string name="tarifasEquipajeFacturadoSR1">Porvenir-P.Williams: 10kg</string>
    <string name="tarifasEquipajeFacturadoSR2">Balmaceda-Ushuaia:20kg</string>
    <string name="tarifasCambiosAntesBR">Not allowed</string>
    <string name="tarifasDevolucionBR">Not allowed</string>
    <string name="tarifasCambiosDespuesBR">Not allowed</string>
    <string name="tarifasEquipajeManoBR">5kg</string>
    <string name="tarifasEquipajeFacturadoBR1">Porvenir-P.Williams: 10kg</string>
    <string name="tarifasEquipajeFacturadoBR2">Balmaceda-Ushuaia:20kg</string>
    <string name="tarifasCambiosAntesVR">Allows changes up to 48 hrs before without charge, after that time does NOT allow</string>
    <string name="tarifasDevolucionVR1">P.Williams- Balmaceda: Allows up to 75% of the fare, must be requested up to 48 hrs before the flight</string>
    <string name="tarifasCambiosDespuesVR1">P.Williams: Allows revalidate the ticket with a charge of 75% of the value of the fare until 72 hrs after the flight.</string>
    <string name="tarifasEquipajeManoVR">5kg</string>
    <string name="tarifasEquipajeFacturadoVR1">Porvenir-P.Williams: 10kg</string>
    <string name="tarifasEquipajeFacturadoVR2">Balmaceda-Ushuaia:20kg</string>
    <string name="tarifasCambiosAntesYR1">Porvenir: Allows changes up to 48 hrs. before the flight without charge, after that time does NOT allow</string>
    <string name="tarifasCambiosAntesYR2">P.Williams- Balmaceda: Allows changes up to 24 hrs. before the flight without charge, after that time does NOT allow</string>
    <string name="tarifasCambiosAntesYR3">Ushuaia: Allows changes until the same day of the flight without charge</string>
    <string name="tarifasDevolucionYR1">Porvenir:Allows up to 75% of the fare, must be requested up to 48 hrs before the flight</string>
    <string name="tarifasDevolucionYR2">P.Williams- Balmaceda: Allow up to 85% of the fare, it must be requested up to 48 hrs before the flight</string>
    <string name="tarifasDevolucionYR3">Ushuaia: Allow 100% of the fare, it must be requested up to 48 hrs before the flight</string>
    <string name="tarifasCambiosDespuesYR">P.Williams It allows revalidate the ticket with a charge of 75% of the value of the fare until 72 hrs after the flight</string>
    <string name="tarifasEquipajeManoYR">5kg</string>
    <string name="tarifasEquipajeFacturadoYR1">Porvenir-P.Williams: 10kg</string>
    <string name="tarifasEquipajeFacturadoYR2">Balmaceda-Ushuaia:20kg</string>
    <string name="tarifasDevolucionVR2">Ushuaia: It allows up to 85% of the fare, it must be requested up to 48 hrs before the flight</string>
    <string name="tarifasCambiosDespuesVR2">Balmaceda-Ushuaia: Not allowed</string>
    <string name="tarifaS">Fare S</string>
    <string name="tarifaB">Fare B</string>
    <string name="tarifaV">Fare V</string>
    <string name="tarifaY">Fare Y</string>
    <string name="tarifaPromo">PROMO</string>
    <string name="tarifaNormal">NORMAL</string>
    <string name="tarifaFlex">FLEX</string>
    <string name="tarifaFull">FULL FLEX</string>
    <string name="tarifasTextoCabecera">Know in detail the options offered by each rate and freely choose the one that best suits you.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_equipaje">"Baggage Policy "</string>
    <string name="equipajeManoTitulo">Hand Luggage</string>
    <string name="equipajeManoDetalle1">Personal effects, carried by the passenger inside the cabin, under his or her own care and responsibility. Each passenger is allowed one personal item, such as a handbag, a small backpack, a baby bag, a jacket, cane, umbrella, small photo camera, reading material or a bag, not exceeding 5 kilos of weight, otherwise it will be put in the aircraft hold.</string>
    <string name="equipajeManoDetalle2">For smaller aircraft care must be taken to carry hand luggage as small as possible; for BAe and 737 units, the maximum size is 43x41x21 cm.</string>
    <string name="equipajeBodegaTitulo">Hold Luggage</string>
    <string name="equipajeBodegaDetalle1">Refers to all luggage that is checked at the airport, and that is transported in the aircraft\'s hold. The weight and size limit are expressed in the purchased ticket.</string>
    <string name="equipajeBodegaDetalle2">The concept of luggage includes clothing, and personal hygiene items, excluding fragile or perishable objects, and damage to said items is not covered by the airline. For the transportation of other species, the passenger may use the cargo service, which includes cargo insurance in case of damage or loss.</string>
    <string name="equipajeRecomTitulo">Recommendation for objects of value</string>
    <string name="equipajeRecomDetalle1">We can all contribute to making travel safer. Please carry within your hand luggage all objects that are fragile or valuable (money, jewelry, electronic devices, etc.), medicine, documents, keys, so that you carry your most valuable items yourself.</string>
    <string name="equipajeRecomDetalle2">If due to weight or dimensions you need to carry an object of this sort in your hold luggage, please take your time to declare these items at the airport counter.</string>
    <string name="equipajeRecomDetalle3">Aerovías DAP will not transport any luggage which contains objects that could be considered dangerous (gases, corrosive substances, explosives, weapons, etc.)</string>
    <string name="equipajeProhibidoTitulo">Forbidden Items</string>
    <string name="equipajeProDetalle1">It is strictly forbidden to carry any luggage which contains items that may cause harm to passengers, the environment and/or the aircraft.</string>
    <string name="equipajeProDetalle2">Gases (compressed, liquefied, in solution or intensively refrigerated), including aerosols, which are flammable, toxic or harmless such as, butane, oxygen, liquid nitrogen, aerosols containing paralyzing gases, filling tubes for liquefied gas lighters, etc.</string>
    <string name="equipajeProDetalle3">Corrosive, solid or liquid, such as: acids, alkalis, mercury, liquid electrolyte batteries, etc.</string>
    <string name="equipajeProDetalle4">Explosives such as ammunition, fireworks and flares, briefcases with alarm devices, explosives for toy guns, etc.</string>
    <string name="equipajeProDetalle5">Flammable liquids such as fuels, paints, thinners, etc.</string>
    <string name="equipajeProDetalle6">Radioactive material whatever its category.</string>
    <string name="equipajeProDetalle7">Oxidizing materials and organic peroxides, such as: bleaches, fertilizers, etc. Toxic and infectious substances such as: insecticides, pesticides, biological products that contain pathogenic germs, etc.</string>
    <string name="equipajeProDetalle8">Flammable solids such as matches (matches). Weapons, understood as such to any element or object that is made, or can be used, for attack or defense, such as: firearms, bladed weapons, gases, electric shock elements, sharp, sharp, blunt, between which can include batons, axes and sticks or sticks with a weight inside or in the form of breakwater.</string>
    <string name="equipajeExcesoTitulo">Excess Luggage</string>
    <string name="equipajeExcesoDetalle1">There will be a charge for baggage as soon as the baggage limit is exceeded. The luggage limits vary according to the route.</string>
    <string name="equipajeExcesoDetalle2">For travel to Porvenir or Puerto Williams, the luggage allowed is 10 Kg in luggage in the hold plus 5 Kg of hand luggage. Each extra Kg of luggage will have a value of $ 1,530 pesos (CLP).</string>
    <string name="equipajeExcesoDetalle3">For travel to Balmaceda and Ushuaia, the luggage allowed is 20 Kg in luggage in the hold plus 5 Kg of hand luggage. Each extra Kg of luggage will have a value of $ 2,500 pesos (CLP). with a maximum of 30 kilos per passenger.</string>
    <string name="equipajeTextoCabecera">"Get to know the luggage policies in detail and travel with everything you need. "</string>
    <string name="title_activity_informacion">"Travel Informed! "</string>
    <string name="tituloNecesidades">Special Needs</string>
    <string name="infoTituloAsistencia">Special Assistance</string>
    <string name="infoDetalleAsistencia">Special Assistance Passengers requiring any special assistance, such as the use of a wheelchair, oxygen, guide dog or other, must ask and/or inform the company at the moment of purchasing the ticket or up to 48 hours prior to the flight.</string>
    <string name="infoTituloSilla">Wheelchair</string>
    <string name="infoDetalleSilla1">If the passenger uses his/her own wheelchair, there will be no additional charge involved.</string>
    <string name="infoDetalleSilla2">The service provided will be from the counter to the boarding gate or seat of the plane. Once arrived at the destination, the passenger will be accompanied to the terminal door, including baggage retrieval.</string>
    <string name="infoDetalleSilla3">This service must be solicited / informed at the moment of purchasing the ticket or up to 48 hours prior to the flight, at the company offices.</string>
    <string name="infoTituloVision">Passengers with a sight or hearing disability</string>
    <string name="infoDetalleVision1">Passengers capable of communication and understanding of air crew members’ safety instructions, as well as capable of tending to their own needs during the flight in an independent manner, will be able to travel without company. Otherwise, it is necessary for these passengers to travel with the company of an assisting adult during the whole flight.</string>
    <string name="infoDetalleVision2">This situation must be informed at the moment of purchasing the ticket or up to 48 hours prior to the flight, at the company offices.</string>
    <string name="infoTituloEmbarazo">Pregnancy</string>
    <string name="infoDetalleEmbarazo1">From the 28th week of pregnancy, passengers will be required to present a Medical Certificate indicating she has no travel restrictions; from the 36th week she must present a similar Medical Certificate, as well as signing a release of liability document, in case of any medical problems taking place during the flight.</string>
    <string name="infoDetalleEmbarazo2">From the 38th week onwards, air travel will not be permitted.</string>
    <string name="infoTituloCirugia">Surgery</string>
    <string name="infoDetalleCirugia1">All passengers subject to surgery up to 10 days before the flight will be demanded a Medical Certificate regarding no travel restrictions, and signing a release of liability document, in case of any medical problems taking place during the flight.</string>
    <string name="infoDetalleCirugia2">This situation must be informed at the moment of purchasing the ticket or up to 48 hours prior to the flight, at the company offices.</string>
    <string name="infoTituloNinos">Travelling with Children</string>
    <string name="infoTituloBebe">Newly Born</string>
    <string name="infoDetalleBebe">Newborn Children are allowed to travel after the seventh day of birth. If travelling sooner is required, a medical certificate signed by a pediatrician is required.</string>
    <string name="infoTituloInfante">Children between 0 – 1 year and 11 months old</string>
    <string name="infoDetalleInfante">Children of this age will travel in the arms of an accompanying adult. Adults travelling with more than a single child between 7 days and 2 years old must make sure the second child is accompanied by another adult, otherwise they must provide a special chair to be attached safely to the seat, in accordance to the required safety measures.</string>
    <string name="infoTituloMenor">Children between 2 and 11 years old</string>
    <string name="infoDetalleMenor1">Must travel in the company of an adult (over 18 years old).</string>
    <string name="infoDetalleMenor2">The company has a service of accompanying a child travelling alone, free of charge, for children in the age of 6 to 11 years old. This service must be solicited at the moment of purchasing the ticket or up to 48 hours prior to the flight, at the company offices.</string>
    <string name="infoTituloJoven">Children between 12 and 17 years old</string>
    <string name="infoDetalleJoven1">May travel on their own. If preferred, the service of accompanying a child travelling alone may be solicited, free of charge.</string>
    <string name="infoDetalleJoven2">This service must be solicited at the moment of purchasing the ticket or up to 48 hours prior to the flight, at the company offices.</string>
    <string name="infoTituloMascota">Pets</string>
    <string name="preguntasTituloCabecera">At Aerovias DAP we like you to travel informed. Everything you need, find it here!</string>
    <string name="preguntasEquipaje">Luggage Policy</string>
    <string name="preguntasInformacion">Information for your Trip</string>
    <string name="preguntasTarifas">Rate Policy</string>
    <string name="preguntasTerminos">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="checkInDescargando">Downloading Boarding Pass...</string>
    <string name="title_activity_boarding">Boarding Pass</string>
    <string name="boardingHeader">Here you will find all your boarding passes that you have made with our application</string>
    <string name="boardingVacio">You have not made any Check In with our application yet</string>
    <string name="menuBoarding">My Boarding Pass</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tickets">My Tickets</string>
    <string name="ticketHeader">Here you will find all your tickets that you have bought using our application</string>
    <string name="ticketVacio">You have not made any purchases with our application yet</string>
    <string name="menuTickets">My Tickets</string>
    <string name="misArchivos">My files</string>
    <string name="infoMascota1">Domestic animals, such as dogs, cats and others may be transported in the company of a responsible adult.</string>
    <string name="infoMascota2">On BAe plans, a maximum of 2 pets in cabin and a maximum of 3 pets in the luggage hold will be permitted.</string>
    <string name="infoMascota3">On Twin Otter plane, a maximum of 1 pet in the luggage hold will be permitted. A liability releas must be signed for the pet, and it cannot weight over 5 kilo including the container/cage.</string>
    <string name="infoMascota4">Pets cannot be carried in King Air or Cessna aircraft.</string>
    <string name="infoTituloPetBodega">In the luggage hold (AVIH)</string>
    <string name="infoPetBodega1">For the acceptance of animals in the luggage hold, the following aspects are taken into account:</string>
    <string name="infoPetBodega2">–\tThe container used must allow at least 10 cm between the standing animal and the top, or ceiling. –\tThe container must have an absorbent surface on its floor. –\tThe container cannot be seriously damaged. –\tMetal locks must be added to the lock of the barrel. –\tThe pet must be with its valid vaccines and present a veterinary certificate. –\tAnimals of brachiocephalic (or flat-nosed) breeds will embark only with a limit of responsibility. –\tThis service must be requested up to 48 hours before the flight –\tAt the airport, animals that are not confirmed by reservation will not be accepted. –\tThis service will have an independent cost of the baggage allowance that will be charged directly at the airport. –\tThe pet must have at least eight weeks (2 months) of age to be accepted. –\tAs a precaution, violent, dead, sick and pregnant animals will not be accepted, except for duly managed exceptions, signing a of responsibility release. –\tA maximum of 1 pet per container will be accepted.</string>
    <string name="infoTituloPetCabina">In Cabin (PETC)</string>
    <string name="infoPetCabina1">For the acceptance of animals in the cockpit of the aircraft we must consider the following aspects:</string>
    <string name="infoPetCabina2">– The pet must have at least eight weeks (2 months) of age to be accepted. – The maximum weight is 5 kg including the container. – The measures of the container should be maximum 30 cm long, x33 cm wide x 17 cm tall. – A maximum of 1 pet per container will be accepted. – The pet must be with its valid vaccines and present a veterinary certificate. – Animals of brachiocephalic (or flat-nosed) breeds will embark only with a limit of responsibility. – This service must be requested up to 48 hours before the flight – At the airport, animals that are not confirmed by reservation will not be accepted.</string>
    <string name="infoTituloPetTarifa">Rate for the transfer of pets</string>
    <string name="infoPetTarifa1">Pet in cabin or hold of BAe $ 1,000 CLP per kilo of weight.</string>
    <string name="infoPetTarifa2">Pet in hold of Twin Otter $ 1,500 CLP per kilo of weight.</string>
    <string name="infoTextoCabecera">Do you have any special needs? !We are here to help you!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_condiciones">" General Conditions"</string>
    <string name="condicionesTitulo">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="condicionesTexto1">The present passenger ticket attest to the celebration and the conditions of the air transport contract celebrating between Aerovías DAP and the passenger whose name appears on this ticket. The aeronautical code of the Republic of Chile, law 18.916. Shall govern in addition to the contract of carriage. It will prevail in all that can not be renounced between the parties.</string>
    <string name="condicionesTexto2">The conditions of return, change or reissue of the air ticket are expressed below for each type of available fare, which are known and accepted by the passenger at the time of acquiring the ticket. In virtue of the foregoing, the provider Aerovías DAP, expressly states that there is no right to retract pursuant to the provisions of Article 3 bis of Law 19,496.</string>
    <string name="condicionesTexto3">Al passengers must be present at the airport counter 2 hrs before the scheduled flight, as indicated on their ticket. The flight closes 40 minutes before the hour, so as to carry on with all aspects before embark. Any passenger present after the time limit will not be embarked.</string>
    <string name="condicionesTituloEquipaje">Issues with luggage</string>
    <string name="condicionesTextoEquipaje1">In case of destruction or loss of luggage that takes place during air transport, compensation will be limited up to 0,15 UF per kg. with a weight limit corresponding to the maximum allowed luggage weight of the respective flight route.</string>
    <string name="condicionesTextoEquipaje2">The passenger must inform of the situation before abandoning the luggage retrieval area, by filing a formal complaint indicating his or her ID document, boarding pass and luggage ticket. In case the passenger has left the airport, the complaint must be filed back at the DAP counter in the airport.</string>
    <string name="condicionesTextoEquipaje3">Aerovías DAP will NOT be responsible for damage that results from normal use, such as:</string>
    <string name="condicionesTextoEquipaje4">•\tMinor cuts, scratches, unstitches, stains or broken zippers. •\tDamage to wheels, base, extensible handles, external pockets. •\tDamage resulting from excess weight. •\tLoss of pieces that project from the luggage, such as handles, pockets, locks, or straps. •\tBasically, damage that does not compromise the function of the luggage: contain personal items. •\tDamage sustained prior to the flight service with Aerovías DAP.</string>
    <string name="condicionesTituloRespon">Limits of Liability</string>
    <string name="condicionesTextoRespon1">In cases of destruction or loss of baggage that occurs during its air transportation, paid compensations will be limited to the amount of 0.15 UF per kilo with a maximum of 10 kilos. For this to be effective, it is a requirement that the passenger give written notice at DAP’s service counter in the airport immediately upon arrival at destination.</string>
    <string name="condicionesTextoRespon2">Only for reasons attributable to the company, when a flight is suspended, passengers will be relocated on subsequent flights or 100% of the value of the ticket will be reimbursed. In all, the company is not responsible for other expenses that could take place for the passenger.</string>
    <string name="condicionesTextoRespon3">Aerovias DAP can refuse or condition the transportation of those passengers whose condition or state constitutes a safety hazard or requires special care during the flight.</string>
    <string name="condicionesTextoCabecera">At Aerovias DAP we like to be transparent and to be aware of the conditions of our service.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_contacto_web">ContactoWeb</string>
</resources>
